<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Holiday Ideas &#8211; Rent</title>
	<atom:link href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/category/holiday-ideas/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 07:03:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/tenerife-fav-60x60.png</url>
	<title>Holiday Ideas &#8211; Rent</title>
	<link>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The most beautiful beaches</title>
		<link>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/21/the-most-beautiful-beaches/</link>
					<comments>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/21/the-most-beautiful-beaches/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rent_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 10:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Holiday Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hospitality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kealakekua]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[holiday ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hospitality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo1.wprentals.org/?p=240</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Located just 30 minutes from the Seychelles International Airport and 45 minutes from the jetty in Victoria, our hotel is ideally situated for day trips to other islands in the archipelago. Whether you choose to join a Seychelles island hopping tour with one of our trusted travel partners, or to explore the islands at your ...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>Located just 30 minutes from the Seychelles International Airport and 45 minutes from the jetty in Victoria, our hotel is ideally situated for day trips to other islands in the archipelago. Whether you choose to join a Seychelles island hopping tour with one of our trusted travel partners, or to explore the islands at your own leisure, be sure not to miss these island highlights:</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>PRASLIN:</strong></p>
<p>The second largest of the Seychelles’ islands, neighbouring Praslin is home to the legendary Vallée de Mai. This valley of towering palms, once believed to be the original site of the Garden of Eden, is a UNESCO World Heritage Site and home to the rare coco de mer and the Seychelles black parrot. Then on to Anse Lazio, one of the Seychelles’ most magnificent beaches. During your Praslin adventure, you will have time to enjoy a delicious Creole buffet lunch of freshly grilled fish, piquant curries simmering in coconut milk and fresh fruits.</p>
<p><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" fetchpriority="high" class="wp-image-36106 size-full alignnone" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island-1.jpeg" alt="" width="900" height="600" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island-1.jpeg 900w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island-1-300x200.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island-1-768x512.jpeg 768w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island-1-240x160.jpeg 240w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></a></p>
<p><strong>LA DIGUE:</strong></p>
<p>La Digue has a unique atmosphere, where the rhythms of true island living still beat loud, and where the bicycle and ox-cart are the main modes of transport. Take a leisurely bicycle ride through palm-lined avenues to Anse Source d’Argent, which is counted among the finest (and certainly the most photographed)&nbsp;<a title="Best Beaches" href="https://www.kempinski.com/en/baie-lazare/seychelles-resort/local-information/best-beaches/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-id="211211">beaches</a> in the world. La Digue beaches are truly in a class of their own, with their imposing granite boulders that meet crystalline waters on a beaches of the softest, pure-white sand.</p>
<p><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island2-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-36108 size-full" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island2-1.jpeg" alt="" width="900" height="505" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island2-1.jpeg 900w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island2-1-300x168.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island2-1-768x431.jpeg 768w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/island2-1-805x453.jpeg 805w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></a></p>
<p><strong>ST ANNE:</strong></p>
<p>As a trip approaches, anxiety increases for guests. Where do I need to go? How do I get there? How will I get a key for the space? How do I plan what to do on my trip? Put your guest at ease by giving them all of the info they’ll need up front instead of making them wait until the last minute. This establishes trust right away and will most likely garner you a great review, and great reviews lead to bookings.</p>
<p><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-35386 size-full" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1.jpeg" alt="" width="930" height="523" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1.jpeg 930w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1-300x169.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1-768x432.jpeg 768w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1-805x453.jpeg 805w" sizes="(max-width: 930px) 100vw, 930px" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/21/the-most-beautiful-beaches/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eat like a local</title>
		<link>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/21/how-to-be-a-great-host/</link>
					<comments>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/21/how-to-be-a-great-host/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rent_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 10:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Holiday Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hospitality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kealakekua]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[holiday ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hospitality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo1.wprentals.org/?p=230</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elle put together some easy steps every host can follow to prevent hosting from becoming more of a chore than a reward. “Some of our most enthusiastic hosts are so dedicated to their guests having an exceptional stay that they’re challenged to find their own time and resources for themselves,” says Elle. “They’re givers and ...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elle put together some easy steps every host can follow to prevent hosting from becoming more of a chore than a reward.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Some of our most enthusiastic hosts are so dedicated to their guests having an exceptional stay that they’re challenged to find their own time and resources for themselves,” says Elle. “They’re givers and sometimes givers swing too far into that giving activity.”</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food2-2.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-36096 size-full" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food2-2.jpeg" alt="" width="900" height="600" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food2-2.jpeg 900w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food2-2-300x200.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food2-2-768x512.jpeg 768w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food2-2-240x160.jpeg 240w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></a></p>
<p>The saying “You have to taste a culture to understand it” certainly holds very true for the Seychelles. Food in the Seychelles is a melting pot of cultural influences that have been blended with the islands’ natural bounty of fruits, spices and ocean-fresh seafood. Here are our top picks of places to experience authentic Creole cuisine:</p>
<p><strong>MARIE-ANTOINETTE</strong></p>
<p>This Seychelles restaurant is housed in a hundred-year-old colonial-style building in the heart of Victoria. As the Seychelles’ oldest restaurant, this establishment serves up delicious food prepared according to traditional Creole recipes. In fact, the menu has not changed much since the restaurant first opened in 1972, and you can still enjoy Creole specialities such as battered parrot fish, octopus curry and Chauve Souris Frugivore (curried fruit bat).</p>
<p><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food3-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-36100 size-full" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food3-1.jpeg" alt="" width="900" height="600" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food3-1.jpeg 900w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food3-1-300x200.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food3-1-768x512.jpeg 768w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food3-1-240x160.jpeg 240w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></a></p>
<p><strong>Opening hours:</strong></p>
<p>Monday to Saturday: 12:00-14:30 (Lunch) | 18:30-21:00 (Dinner)</p>
<p><strong>BAZAR LABRIN</strong></p>
<p>Every Wednesday night, the Seychelles’ most popular beach, Beau Vallon, is transformed into a vibrant market with colourful stalls appearing at the side of the road, selling popular Seychelles street food at traditional prices. Fresh fruit juices, handmade souvenirs and local artwork are also on sale, lending a kaleidoscopic ambience to the evening. As the sun sinks below the horizon, twinkling bonfires light up on the beach for the Seychelles’ traditional moutay dance.</p>
<p><strong>Opening hours:</strong></p>
<p>Wednesdays: 16:30-21:00</p>
<p><strong>STREET FOOD IN VICTORIA</strong></p>
<p>The narrow streets of Victoria are lined with tiny shops and food stalls, each offering a unique insight into the culinary culture of the Seychelles. Take a stroll through the bustling capital and make sure to sample local Creole cuisine while searching for souvenirs and admiring the local architecture. Not to be missed is Callino’z, serving classical street bites from Jardin de Enfants, opposite the Convention Centre.</p>
<p><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food-2.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone wp-image-36093 size-full" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food-2.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="576" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food-2.jpeg 1024w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food-2-300x169.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food-2-768x432.jpeg 768w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/food-2-805x453.jpeg 805w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a></p>
<p>How to get there: A taxi from the hotel costs roughly EUR 50* or, for an authentically local experience, take the public bus. There is a bus stop on the West Coast Road, just 10 minutes from the hotel’s main gate. A ticket costs EUR 0.30*.</p>
<p><strong>LE JARDIN DE SEYCHELLOIS</strong></p>
<p>Of course, it is possible to enjoy traditional Creole cuisine without ever having to leave the resort. Every fifth night, the buffet dinners at Café Lazare are transformed into a celebration of local cuisine with our weekly Creole extravaganza. Simmering curries, grilled fish and piles of fresh fruits are just some of the local favourites that we invite you to sample.</p>
<p><strong>CATCH OF THE DAY</strong></p>
<p>The Seychelles is home to some of the richest fishing grounds in the world, where angling has become a way of life. It’s no surprise, then, that grilled fish is a staple of Creole cuisine. There is no better way to enjoy this simple, yet delicious dish than if you’ve caught the fish yourself. Bring back the day’s catch from your latest fishing expedition and our chefs will gladly prepare it for you.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/21/how-to-be-a-great-host/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Things to do in Tenerife</title>
		<link>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/21/5-things-to-do-in-tenerife/</link>
					<comments>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/21/5-things-to-do-in-tenerife/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rent_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 10:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Holiday Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hospitality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kealakekua]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[holiday ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hospitality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo1.wprentals.org/?p=220</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you can bear to tear yourself away from some of the most beautiful beaches in the world, then there are plenty of exciting experiences to encounter on the Seychelles’ largest island. For visitors wondering what to do on Mahé, here are some of our recommendations (in no order of preference): hospitality can come through ...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>If you can bear to tear yourself away from some of the most beautiful beaches in the world, then there are plenty of exciting experiences to encounter on the Seychelles’ largest island. For visitors wondering what to do on Mahé, here are some of our recommendations (in no order of preference):</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/header_image-e1630394162607-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" src="https://solo.wprentals.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/header_image-1024x649.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-35364"/></a></figure>



<p>hospitality can come through in a lot of ways, but it most definitely starts with a clean space. And while cleaning might not be the most fun part of hosting, it doesn’t have to be difficult! Here are a few tips and tricks to help you get swept up in an effective and easy cleaning routine.</p>



<p><strong>1. HIKING IN MAHÉ</strong></p>



<p>Mahé Island’s unique granitic landscape offers visitors the opportunity to hike and walk in areas of untouched natural beauty. More than 20% of this island’s landmass is protected by national parks, including Morne Seychellois National Park which is home to Mahé’s tallest mountain, Morne Seychellois (2,969 ft). Vistas of unparalleled beauty are promised to those who reach its summit. Hikers can explore the Seychelles’ highest peaks and trek along trails to otherwise inaccessible beaches, such as Anse Major. Gentler walks and excursions that allow you to explore waterfalls, swim in natural pools and take pictures of indigenous flora and Seychelles wildlife can also be recommended.</p>



<p><strong>2. </strong>FEED THE TURTLES</p>



<p>No trip to the Seychelles is complete without a visit to island nation’s colourful capital, Victoria. As the smallest capital city in Africa, it won’t take you long to see all of the highlights this vibrant little borough has to offer. Set aside a morning to visit places of interest, such as</p>



<ul>
<li>The Victoria Clock Tower</li>



<li>The kaleidoscopic Sir Selwyn Selwyn-Clarke Market</li>



<li>Arul Mihu Navasakthi Vinayagar Temple</li>
</ul>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="930" height="523" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-35386" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1.jpeg 930w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1-300x169.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1-768x432.jpeg 768w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/island_turtle-1-805x453.jpeg 805w" sizes="(max-width: 930px) 100vw, 930px" /></a></figure></div>


<p><strong>3. VISIT A TROPICAL GARDEN</strong></p>



<p>As the Seychelles was once believed to be the original Garden of Eden, it is no surprise that rare and exceptional species of plants and flowers flourish in this tropical environment. These can best be experienced in curated gardens, such as the Seychelles Botanical Garden in Victoria or Le Jardin du Roi Spice Garden in Anse Royale. Learn about the domestic and medicinal uses of various plants and shrubs in the Seychelles’ households and enjoy a meal prepared using home-grown herbs and spices.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/garden-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="768" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/garden-1.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-36078" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/garden-1.jpeg 1024w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/garden-1-300x225.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/garden-1-768x576.jpeg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a></figure>



<p><strong>4. VISIT A RUM/TEA FACTORY</strong></p>



<p>Experience the spirit of the Seychelles with a tour of the Takamaka rum distillery at Le Plaine St André. The Takamaka rum distillery was built and developed by brothers Richard and Bernard d’Offay in 2002. Their vision was to provide the Seychelles islands with high-quality rum based on their grandfather’s original recipe. The distillery can be found on a historic plantation estate, which is now the home of the Seychelles’ most popular spirit. The tour will be followed by a professional tasting of the products, made from purified spring water and island-grown sugarcane.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/tea_factory-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="900" height="675" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/tea_factory-1.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-36081" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/tea_factory-1.jpeg 900w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/tea_factory-1-300x225.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/tea_factory-1-768x576.jpeg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></a></figure>



<p><strong>5. VISIT A WATERFALL</strong></p>



<p>With Mahé’s mountainous landscape, it is no surprise that the island has several impressive waterfalls worth visiting. One of the most impressive – and easily accessible – is Sauzier Waterfall in Port Glaud. Just a short walk from the main road, a cascade of fresh mountain water tumbles down moss-covered rocks into an inviting pool below. Perfect for swimming and a unique photo opportunity, this popular attraction can get quite crowded – so we recommend getting there early.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/waterfall-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="900" height="601" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/waterfall-1.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-36082" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/waterfall-1.jpeg 900w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/waterfall-1-300x200.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/waterfall-1-768x513.jpeg 768w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/waterfall-1-240x160.jpeg 240w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></a></figure>



<p>Spend an hour or two savouring the view or enjoying a refreshing swim, before venturing off to explore other attractions in the area, such as the Seychelles Tea Factory, SMAC Adventures Zip Line and Port Launay.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/21/5-things-to-do-in-tenerife/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Planning a Honeymoon in Tenerife</title>
		<link>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/20/planning-a-honeymoon-in-tenerife/</link>
					<comments>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/20/planning-a-honeymoon-in-tenerife/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rent_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 13:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Hawaii]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holiday Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hospitality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[holiday ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hospitality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo1.wprentals.org/?p=192</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Hawaii honeymoon is ideal for couples who enjoy a mix of beach, culture and bar hopping. From the vibrant nightlife to the rich historical sites, and lush, tropical beaches, Cancun is just made for excitement and romance. Luxury Retreats’ villas only enhance the honeymoon experience. From the ocean facing private terraces, with alfresco Jacuzzis, ...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Hawaii honeymoon is ideal for couples who enjoy a mix of beach, culture and bar hopping. From the vibrant nightlife to the rich historical sites, and lush, tropical beaches, Cancun is just made for excitement and romance. Luxury Retreats’ villas only enhance the honeymoon experience.</p>
<p><a href="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/beach-sand-1.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-36062" src="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/beach-sand-1.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="616" srcset="httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/beach-sand-1.jpeg 1024w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/beach-sand-1-300x180.jpeg 300w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/beach-sand-1-768x462.jpeg 768w, httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/beach-sand-1-400x242.jpeg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a></p>
<p>From the ocean facing private terraces, with alfresco Jacuzzis, hammocks, and sun loungers to the opulent, open plan living spaces, with sleek furnishings, floor-to-ceiling windows, a fully equipped kitchen with travertine countertops, and oversized bedrooms with en-suite bathrooms featuring steam rooms and whirlpool baths, our homes in the region have everything you could wish for.</p>
<blockquote><p>Whenever I get asked to recommend a destination for honeymoon, I always have the same reply. If you are looking for sun, luxury and a trip of a lifetime……there is only one place for me…..Cancun, Mexico.</p></blockquote>
<p>Cancun is the sort of destination that has something for everyone. My husband loves to be adventurous and active on holidays, whereas I like to chill out and switch off. When we were deciding on where we would like to go on honeymoon, we went through many destinations until we found this one that matched our criteria.</p>
<p><a href="https://tenerife.wprentals.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/bedroom_1024-2.jpeg"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-36065" src="https://tenerife.wprentals.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/bedroom_1024-2.jpeg" alt="" width="756" height="408"></a></p>
<p>We booked with American Holidays and took in a few days in Orlando before flying out to Cancun. We booked at an event that American Holidays run every year. They have the Red Cow Sale which is held in the Red Cow Moran Hotel in Dublin but my understanding is that they roll out the deals online too. We saved just over €1000 on our package.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>httpmuhammadfuzail.github.io/Rent/2015/04/20/planning-a-honeymoon-in-tenerife/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
